fresherpage.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy - Homepage.org

Homepage.org Privacy Policy  

Thank you for reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your Privacy is very important   
to us and we’re committed to protecting it.   

What type of information we collect  
  
The server on which the web site is located collects and saves the   
default information customarily logged by web server software. Such  
information usually includes the date and time of your visit, originating  
IP address, and pages and images requested.  
  
The web site and third party advertisers may use cookies to keep track  
of web searches you make while visiting this web site as well as your  
web surfing behavior on this web site and other web sites you may visit  
to enhance your online experience and learn more about how you use  
this web site in order to improve the quality of services.  

Third Parties Disclosure  
  
We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you  
visit our web site. These companies may use aggregated non-personal   
information about your visit to this and other web sites in order to   
provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
Such use is not based on personal identifying information and does not  
include your name, address, email address or telephone number. In such   
cases we require that third parties comply with our privacy policy and   
any other confidentiality and security measures.  
  
We may use the information you provide us for auditing, research   
and statistical analysis to improve our web site and its services such   
as customizable hyperlink option and content. Again such use is not   
based on personal identifying information.   
  
In limited circumstances including legal processes, fraud prevention  
or imminent harm we may have to share some information with legal  
authorities or third parties to ensure network security and services.  

Use of Cookies   
  
A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent  
to your computer when you visit a web site. Cookies used by this   
web site may store information such as user preferences. You can  
reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is  
being sent. However, without cookies some web site features or services   
may not function properly.  

DoubleClick Dart Cookies  
  
We feature Google custom search on this web site and as a result, we  
may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick which  
is sent to your computer when you’re browsing the web and visit a site  
using DoubleClick advertising (for instance for Google AdSense ads). The  
purpose of this cookie is to identify and serve ads specifically selected to   
serve your interests based on your previous browsing history; this is also   
known as interest based targeting advertising. Again, such use of DART  
cookies is not based on personal identifying information and does not  
include your name, address, email address, telephone number or any  
credit card information.  

Web Site Servers  
  
This web site processes personal information on servers in the United  
States and Canada. The origin of this web site is in Canada.  

Use of Contact Information  
  
We may use your contact information to (1) send you updates on new  
features or services of this web site, or (2) to inform you of the launch   
of new web sites that we believe are of significance to the theme and   
culture of Homepage.org.
